Hey there!
We are here at Odakata Yurikazu!
I'm a student and I'm making curry.
Make curry?
It's like a curry battle.
Battle?
Hello!
Hi, I'm Chartary!
What kind of sauce do you make?
We put chocolate,
We make a sauce with a lot of depth.
Pictures!
One, two, three.
Three, two, one.
Thank you!
Ah!
What? Oh, no!
Oh, no!
Not here, not here.
It's expensive.
Make love into a chain.
I'll send some from afar.
About this much.
Please make love a chain.
Looks like you can eat, Ueda-san.
Yes, a bit contracted here.
Contracted Ya-ya.
Thank you.
Sit down, sit down.
Wow, what a restaurant manager sitting down sitting down sitting down.
Once it's hot.
Bon appétit.
Suddenly?
You startled me.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It's delicious!
Chocolate!
The taste of chocolate!
I can feel it!
Yummy!
I feel the chocolate!
You're going to eat this?
Eat this and eat this.
You're not going to eat this?
Is "yummy" Korean?
I've never eaten anything like this.
Oh, I don't know. I've never had it before.
Mashito.
I'm serious.
I'll try my best.
I want to eat so much!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's delicious.
It was hard when I ate meat.
But the rice cakes...
It was really good. It was delicious.
It was delicious.
It's so good.
It's so good. It's so good. It's so good.
It's delicious.
Delicious. Delicious.
Tteokbokki is better than curry
Looks delicious!
Delicious.
Too sweet? In Korea.
Dr. Arius eats it.
Curry?
We eat Dr. Arius.
It's beautiful.
So, what's missing in Japanese food? Overall.
So when I come to Japan, I don't eat pretty food.
I'm very satisfied when I eat pretty things.Because eating pretty food is so satisfying.
Really get together and eat something pretty.
soooooo
Foot tightening hurt
It's thick, isn't it?
ol
No, it's not.
Oh! Is that right?
I think so!
Thank you!
It's so green.
This is it.
It's done.
It's so pretty!
Looks delicious.
Thank you.
It's lovely.
Friends?
I'd say it was a great success.
All's well that ends well.
Korea's the best!
Cheers!
feel
ni
Looks really good!
It's good, right?
Yum!
Sweet potatoes are good.
It's good.
It's sweet.
It's spicy.
It's spicy, but...
Bon appétit
Thank you very much
Delicious
It's so good!
It looks
It looks spicy.
but it is sweeter than I expected.
But the sweetness is also
but it also has a spicy flavor.
A taste that is neither Japanese nor
A taste not found in Korea or Japan
Delicious
A new world
I saw a new world.
You're not a pro, are you?
I'm glad.
If it's a new world, then it's a success.
It's the only way to taste it.
There's no such thing as a one-size-fits-all.
It's good.
Like Mento.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
Thank you for the food
Thank you for your hard work
Bon appétit
Good night
Delicious.
Ah!
Delicious!
Rare and not too spicy
Just right
Sweet.
It's good?
It was good.
It's good.
Yum. Yum.
Who are you playing with?
Oh, you want to shake a leg at him?
Yes, ma'am.
Yummy.
Exchange, exchange, exchange.Exchange Exchange
Any of them
Exchange Exchange
Looks good.
Is the rice bad?
It's hard.
What?
Hard!
Hard.
Easy to do.
What? This is bad.
It's bad.
It doesn't taste good.
Let's put some water in.
Turn it on.
Here.
Yeah. - Yeah, it's good.
Yeah, it's good.
Not too hard? It's not hard.
Oh, that's good. That's great.
Good, good, good, good, good.
This is dark.
You can drink nothing.
I'll drink it tomorrow.
Drink it or not.
Okay, well, I'd like to announce the results.
I'd like to announce the third place and the first place in that order.
We've prepared the products.
Okay, I'll start with the contents.
Third place
Roppers!
Amazing!
Yummy!
Delicious!
I think of it as a challenge to make a curry with shrimp in it.
The sweetness of the shrimp and the spices were a perfect match.
I say theo tam mash was all over the place.
Yes, applause!
I was pulling so hard.
I pulled it off so much!
Glad to hear it.
Yes, well, I'll announce the second place.
Yes, please.
Second place, number 5.
Number five.
Oh!
There it is again.
Uh-oh.
Chain of love, please.
I'll send a little from afar.
That's about it.
Sorry.
Chain of love, please.
It's a different one.
It's like a soup curry, but with a sour and light curry flavor, and a lot of ingredients and a lot of ingredients.
Please join us if you get tired of eating too!
Yes, applause!
Thank you very much for your hard work!
I see that Uira's team is still here.
You, too, Wylla.
We're still here.
The winner is No. 3!
The rice is hard!
It's hard!
Hard!
What? This is bad! It's disgusting!
Put some water in it!
The spiciness was just right, with a nice spicy kick.
The size of the ingredients and the size of the meat were also good.
Congratulations on the first place.
Thank you very much.
Did you expect to win?
Yes, I did.
You have to leave it at home, at home.
Because it's the best.
It was the best.It was the best.
What was the point that won you the first place?
It was the bond.
The bond.
It's the bond.
Also, I'm a little confident in my secret ingredient.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's chocolate,
Not regular chocolate, but Anpanman chocolate.
Oh! Shrinkage!
Shrinkage!
Yay!
Ah! Oh, yeah! It's perfect now!
Wow, that's great, from over here.
Pretty big ears.
Miyanami yana, this is good.
Anpanman chocolate!
It's 100 times the cake!
Cake 100 times bigger!
[please subscribe to our channel]
Everything's connected.
Congratulations!
Thank you for watching.
We'd like to get some feedback from you.
Thank you very much.
Here we go. Here we go.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
I know it's been difficult, but I really enjoyed talking with you all.
I had a lot of fun talking to you all and interacting with you.
I'm sure I'll see you all again.
I hope we can get to know each other better then.
Thank you very much.
I hope there will be more opportunities like this in the future, and I hope that we, the Batten Girls Club, will be able to visit again and make curry again. I also hope we can make curry again.
Also, the Japanese curry was the most delicious. Thank you very much.
It was the most delicious! It was the most delicious!
I had a lot of fun making curry with you and you taught me a lot of Korean and we had a lot of fun talking.
It was the most delicious! Thank you very much.
Now, please give a big round of applause again.
Thank you very much.
This is Murakata Taisha Shrine.
Let's go pay our respects together now.
So we will now hold Operation JRC.
Please.
Let's go then.
Pull over, Mr. Sakira!
I won't.
You're making me nervous.
Thank you for your hard work
Bow.
Please bow in front of this door
bow
Please bow here.
In the middle, God passes through
In the middle, God goes through.
He's moving out of the way so much.
He's moving out of the way.
I'm not ready for this.
What do you think?
Traffic safety.
I heard there's one out of three.
Cars that never crash.
I think this place has a road safety god.
Thank you for watching.
I'll clean up.
This is where we wash our hands, clean our hands
We've saved the pictures and the body
We're going to pray here now.
First of all, put your money in this money box
I will bow twice
Two claps
Yes, sir.
I pray or make a wish here
Prayers and requests
When you're done, do one united prayer.
And when you're done, you go back for another round.
I'm in.Contestant.
That's it.
Thank you very much.
We received our customer's favorite sweets.
The sweets are from a candy shop
We received sweets from a candy shop
We received sweets from a confectionery shop
The sweets from the confectionery are from the confectionery
The sweets of the confectionery shop are the sweets of the confectionery shop
The candy shop's candy is the candy shop
Thank you for your hard work
What did you want to ask for?
Me?
I'm president of the student council this year.
I'm going to make sure that there are no accidents.
To get this program off the ground without a hitch.
That's great.
I was in charge yesterday.
I'm going to be here with the car.
the boat is going on board and we are going back to Korea
To prevent accidents like this in the future
so that we can finish this kind of program.
I finished this program.
I'm going back with safety on when I get in the car.
to this for all of you.
Thank you so much.
Here you go.
Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
What do you think?
We'll all be happy and healthy.
Oh.
I wish Japan and Korea to get along better and better
I asked for it.
I hope this program will continue for a second and a third time.
I asked for
Peace.
Peace?
Yes, sir.
Is it?
Certainly.
Have a peaceful day.
Peace.
Congratulations.
I'll be fine.
First dish
First dish.
How was it?
It's so tight.
Don't worry about learning
Study until you enjoy it
You'll be fine there.
thank you
Thank you
Come on in.
I'll talk.
The sweets look good.
Delicious.
I bought two.
I bought two red ones.
I bought two of the red ones.
I bought the health ones
The health ones
You bought three
I bought one for my mom, one for my grandpa, and one for my grandma.
That's nice.
Well, go home.
Give them to me.
Take a long look at it.
It's nice.
I'm going to a place called Takamiya.
He told me to go there in Korean.
Cab da.
Let's go.
You can't say "taxi-da"?
Taxi-da.
Taxi-da.Taxida
Taxida
Taxida.
We'll do it together, YouTube
Batten Girls Club Official
Are you on Google?
You can watch it on this channel.
They were watching our music video earlier.
Thanks for watching!
How did you like the music video?
It was great!
Uncle! Uncle!
You don't usually come here like this?
Us?
I do.
When I'm trying to do my best.
Or when I need to calm down.
I might come.
Oh, my God.
Fireworks!
There's a fireworks show?
College!
In the summer?
Wanna go?
It's gonna be love!
Too many people.
Oh, no.
Oh, what's this...
Wait, this is...
Can we go?
Can you do it?
Yes, it's okay!
It's not coming out!
It's working!
Here it comes!
Let's see, this is... let's see..,
There is a World Heritage Site called Okinawa Island,
And along with it, this is one of the most sacred places in the grounds of Murakata Shrine,
This is one of the most sacred places in the grounds of Murakata Shrine.
This is where the gods are said to have descended.
Oh!
Is it this way?
Yes, this way.
This way, right here.
Is it over there?
Yeah, yeah.
It is said that God came down there,
I guess we're going to pay our respects there, just like before,
What should I do?
Oh, that's good.
Thank you for watching.
Good night.
The Murakata Ambassadors have come around, how was your trip?
It was a fun trip!
Thank you for your time! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
How was your trip, even General Tagata?
I didn't have a chance to chat with Korean students like this
I never had a chance to chat with Korean students like this or make curry together.
It was a lot of fun.
I would like to get to know them better and better.
This time, Korean students came to Japan, but on the other hand
I would like to go to Korea and learn about the local culture there.
When there are big events in Murakata in the future, we would like to learn more about the local culture.
I hope that when we have a big event in Murakata in the future, many people from all over the world
I thought that when we have big events in Murakata in the future, people from all over the world will come and make it fun and exciting.
Murakata will become a more and more enjoyable place.
I don't think I've ever had this kind of opportunity with the Corona Disaster.
I think the biggest thing was that we could finally meet each other.
Also, as we were talking...
Why did you decide to study Japanese?
I asked him why he wanted to study Japanese and why he liked anime.
After hearing those reasons and others
I thought that by promoting the good qualities of Japan and Murakata, we could make people like Japan even more.
I think that we should do our best to promote the good qualities of Japan and the Murata region.
I think we should do our best more and more.
For the first time in three years, people from Japan and Korea met and interacted at the same time.
and we were able to communicate with each other.We were able to interact.
I thought we were much closer than we were before Corona.
Yes, that's right.
I think this is proof that people really feel closer to K-POP and other cultures.
I think it's proof that people really feel closer to K-POP and other cultures.
It's been a long time since I've had this kind of exchange, and I was very moved by it.
Thank you very much.
We had Kusa students here this time.
Next time, I would like to visit Kusa Gaidai University with high school students.
I would like to visit Kusa Gaidai University with high school students next time.
If possible, we would like you to come to Toyama with us.
I'd like you to come to Toyama with us.
Shall we go ashore?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm also looking forward to seeing the students again.
It was the first time for me to see them today.
I'm really looking forward to meeting the students again.
I hope you'll enjoy it even more.
I look forward to seeing you again.
I look forward to meeting you again.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work